(This drama is related to specific characters, institutions, and groups It has nothing to do with the case and is purely fictitious (I hereby inform you)
(본 드라마는 특정 인물, 기관, 집단과 관련되어 있습니다. 해당 사건과 무관하며 순전히 허구입니다. (본 내용을 알려드립니다)
(Seasoning, sesame oil, chili powder)
(양념, 참기름, 고춧가루)
I need someone to follow a guy.
남자를 따라갈 사람이 필요해요.
who do you want to follow
누구를 팔로우하고 싶나요?
Although Douxue will take action against gangsters
Douxue는 갱스터에 대해 조치를 취하지만
But he won't bully innocent people
하지만 그는 무고한 사람들을 괴롭히지는 않을 것입니다
His name is…
그의 이름은…
Li Douxue
리두수에
Usually stalking someone…
보통 누군가를 스토킹하는데…
All for some purpose
모든 것은 어떤 목적을 위해
If you tell me your purpose first
목적을 먼저 말하면
things might go more smoothly
일이 더 순조롭게 진행될 수도 있어요
(Episode 7) You said you have the right to stay in Mingdangdong Dogeng
(7화) 당신은 Mingdangdong Dogeng에 머물 권리가 있다고 했어요
Are there 100 places?
100자리 있어요?
It's true
사실이에요
I heard that the occupancy rights are 20 square meters.
입주권은 20제곱미터라고 들었습니다.
Previously it cost less than 3 million won can buy it
기존에는 300만원 미만이었는데 그것을 살 수 있다
Now it has risen to 40 to 50 million won.
지금은 4000만~5000만 원까지 올랐습니다.
Oh my god
맙소사
first time i saw A place where the price is so ridiculously high
내가 처음 봤을 때 가격이 터무니없이 비싼 곳
What right of occupancy?
점유권은 무엇입니까?
This is not an ordinary apartment building right of occupancy
일반아파트 입주권이 아닌
It is the right to occupy the apartment released during the city update.
도시 업데이트 때 공개된 아파트를 점유할 수 있는 권리입니다.
I heard the competition is very fierce
경쟁이 매우 치열하다고 들었는데
Whether it is Cheong Wa Dae or relevant government departments, Those guys from the city government
청와대든, 정부 관련 부처든, 시정부에서 나온 놈들
All before the news comes out
뉴스가 나오기 전에 다
Just mobilize all your relatives I'm snapping up the land over there.
그냥 친척들 다 동원해 저기 땅을 싹쓸이할 거예요.
So how is the intelligence possible? Has it reached us?
그렇다면 지능은 어떻게 가능한가? 그것이 우리에게 도달했나요?
It's just like war
그냥 전쟁이나 마찬가지야
Take good care and don't let the deadbeat come back.
잘 관리하고 데드비트가 다시 발생하지 않도록 하세요.
It must never happen again The bloody conflict just now
다시는 이런 일이 일어나서는 안 됩니다 지금의 피비린내 나는 갈등
Yes eldest brother
응 큰 형님
I'll come to hand over my shift tomorrow
내일 근무를 인계하러 올게요
Thank you for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
Brother, please come quickly
형님 빨리 와주세요
Got it, brat
알았어, 얘야
Thank you for taking charge of this big case.
이런 큰 사건을 맡아주셔서 감사합니다.
Take one portion and treat the brothers to barbecue
한 부분을 가져다가 형제들에게 바비큐를 대접하세요
Just use the other one where needed.
필요한 경우 다른 하나를 사용하십시오.
Hey what are you looking at
야, 뭘 보고 있는 거야?
Brother, these are really just enough to buy barbecue.
형님, 이거 정말 바비큐 사먹기에 충분해요.
The brothers were injured and paid for medical expenses
형제들은 부상을 입고 치료비를 지불받았습니다
It costs a lot of money…
돈이 많이 든다…
If I make enough How can I only share the money with you?
내가 충분히 벌면 어떻게 돈을 당신하고만 나눌 수 있나요?
What's wrong...
무슨 일이야 ...
Boy, I'm serious
얘야, 나 진심이야
Am I going to give you your hard-earned money? Do you swallow it yourself?
당신이 힘들게 번 돈을 당신에게 줄 건가요? 스스로 삼키나요?
Everything must be accumulated slowly
뭐든 천천히 쌓아야지
If we can continue to take their cases
우리가 계속해서 그들의 사건을 맡을 수 있다면
I will definitely do it then I'll give you a generous bonus, okay?
그럼 꼭 해볼게 보너스를 넉넉하게 드릴게요, 알았죠?
It's time for me to go
이제 갈 시간이야
Jisoo, someone is vomiting in the toilet.
지수야, 누군가 화장실에서 토하고 있어.
Go and clear it quickly
빨리 가서 클리어해
So dirty
너무 더러워
Yes, brother, I will handle it right away
응, 형, 바로 처리할게.
Brother, walk slowly
오빠, 천천히 걸어요
How much does he give
그 사람은 얼마를 주나요?
Two hundred for brothers, one hundred for me
형제에게는 200개, 나는 100개
is he kidding
그 사람 농담하는 거야?
The brothers’ medical expenses alone cost two hundred.
형제들의 의료비만 200달러가 들었습니다.
Damn you guy, this is too much.
젠장, 이건 너무하다.
Go to the baseball stadium and sell tickets to scalpers. I make about the same amount of money as this
야구장에 가서 스캘퍼들에게 티켓을 팔아보세요. 난 이것과 거의 비슷한 돈을 벌고 있어
Bro, give these to the brothers.
형님, 이것을 형제들에게 주세요.
I know
알아요
What about us?
우리는 어떻습니까?
Don’t we get a monthly salary?
우리는 월급을 받지 않나요?
But…
하지만…
Yeah, forget it if I can't subsidize it.
응, 보조금을 받을 수 없으면 잊어버려.
At least we can't drain our brothers dry.
적어도 우리 형제들을 건조하게 만들 수는 없습니다.
Brother, I brought people here
형님, 제가 사람들을 여기로 데려왔어요
let her in
그녀를 들여보내줘
welcome you
환영합니다
(Lee Yunae)
(이윤애)
We suddenly came to you. Did it scare you?
우리는 갑자기 당신에게 왔습니다. 겁이 났나요?
Brother, did he tell you to remit money?
형님, 돈을 송금하라고 했나요?
How much does he want you to wire?
그 사람은 당신에게 얼마를 송금하길 원하나요?
If the boss knew I told him...
사장이 알면 내가 말했을텐데...
I will really die miserably
나 진짜 비참하게 죽을 거야
Don't worry, we will keep it secret
걱정하지 마세요. 비밀로 지켜드리겠습니다.
How much does he want you to wire?
그 사람은 당신에게 얼마를 송금하길 원하나요?
50 million won
5천만원
Fifty million won?
5천만원?
Brother Guangzhuo really called you Do you want to remit 50 million won?
Guangzhuo 형제가 정말로 당신에게 전화했습니다. 5천만원을 송금하시겠습니까?
Yes it's true
네, 사실이에요
Five checks for 10 million won in total
총 1000만원 상당의 수표 5장
He also said that a man should be loyal
남자는 충성해야 한다고도 하더군요
I heard him fart
그 사람 방귀소리 들었어
Really…
정말…
Fifty million won…
5000만원…
Brothers are very unhappy
형제들은 매우 불행하다
Now there is a valid reason
이제 타당한 이유가 생겼습니다
The time has come, right?
때가 왔지, 그렇지?
Just now
지금 막
Douxue, let’s get rid of Guangzhuo.
Douxue, 광주를 없애자.
I can be the first one
내가 첫 번째가 될 수 있어
The time has indeed come
정말 그 때가 왔다
Brother Guangzhuo was not like that before...
Guangzhuo 형제는 예전에는 그렇지 않았습니다 ...
It's not all because of damn greed
그게 다 빌어먹을 욕심 때문은 아니지
Douxue also said
Douxue도 말했다.
He will divide us when there is only petty profit
그는 작은 이익만 있을 때 우리를 나누리라
But when there is gold and silver, he will definitely keep it to himself
그러나 금과 은이 있으면 그는 반드시 그것을 혼자 간직할 것이다.
So…
그래서…
Are you about to take action?
조치를 취하려고 하시나요?
No
아니요
Why not?
왜 안돼?
Because I have the final say
최종 결정권은 나한테 있으니까
Hello Douxue
안녕하세요 Douxue
Douxue
두쉬
Big brother…
형…
(Diagnosis Choi Young-sik) non-obstructive azoospermia
(진단 최영식) 비폐쇄성 무정자증
The date of diagnosis was three months before the wedding
진단일은 결혼 3개월 전이었습니다.
sorry
미안하다
If only I had known earlier
내가 좀 더 일찍 알았더라면
I won’t let Mr. Tetsuo suffer like that.
테츠오 씨를 그런 식으로 괴롭히게 놔두지 않겠습니다.
I'm really sorry
정말 미안해요
The so-called life is really wonderful.
소위 인생은 정말 훌륭합니다.
I really almost...
정말 거의...
Almost...
거의...
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site)
(명당동 철거현장에서 폭력 충돌 발생)
There's something I'm curious about
궁금한게 있는데
You haven't seen Huang Cichang for a long time, right?
황치창을 오랫동안 보지 못하셨나요?
Right
예
Chief Huang, isn't he coming now?
황 과장님, 지금 안 오시나요?
It seems so
그런 것 같아요
Without the backer of Chief Huang,
황 추장의 후원자가 없으면,
My husband will become isolated and helpless.
남편은 고립되고 무력해질 것입니다.
That is to say
즉,
Are we It’s time to find another place to party.
우리는 이제 파티할 다른 장소를 찾을 시간입니다.
Oh my god, Chief Huang, welcome.
맙소사, 황 과장님, 반갑습니다.
We are about to break up the meeting
우리는 회의를 중단하려고 합니다
Everyone, let's go
다들 가자
See you next time Luo
다음에 또 만나요 ​​루오
What a superficial woman
정말 피상적인 여자야
She doesn’t even know her husband I get scolded by my superior every day
그 사람은 자기 남편도 모르고 매일 상사한테 혼나고
Be careful if others overhear you
다른 사람이 당신의 말을 엿듣는다면 조심하세요
So what if I hear it
그럼 내가 들으면 어떡하지?
According to her husband's performance I wouldn't be surprised if I get fired one day
남편의 연기에 따르면 언젠가 해고당하더라도 놀라지 않을 것입니다.
Have you been busy recently?
최근에 바빴나요?
Would you like a cup of coffee?
커피 한 잔 드시겠어요?
No need
필요 없음
Do you want to drink?
마실래?
No, that's not what I need
아니, 그건 나에게 필요한 게 아니야
No matter how busy I am at work
회사에서 아무리 바빠도
How can you skip dinner?
저녁을 어떻게 건너뛸 수 있나요?
People think we eat delicacies from mountains and seas every day
사람들은 우리가 매일 산과 바다의 진미를 먹는다고 생각합니다.
But in fact, we often don’t have time to eat
그런데 사실 밥 먹을 시간이 없는 경우가 많아요
As the saying goes, all it takes is one missed meal
속담처럼, 한 끼만 놓치면 충분하다
No matter how much you eat, you can't make up for it.
아무리 먹어도 보충할 수 없습니다.
So please eat on time
그러니 시간 맞춰서 드세요
Ruzhen, please help me cook.
루젠 씨, 제가 요리하는 것을 도와주세요.
It's not too late to start now
지금 시작해도 늦지 않았습니다
Is that why you came to us so late?
그래서 우리한테 이렇게 늦게 온 거야?
What else should I do?
또 무엇을 해야 합니까?
My mother even called me and asked me to spend the night outside.
어머니는 나에게 전화해서 밖에서 밤을 보내라고 하기도 했다.
I don’t know any relatives in Seoul
서울에 아는 친척이 없어요
You want me, a weak woman, to stay in a hotel Very scary
나약한 여자를 호텔에 묵으라고 하네 매우 무서운
Yes, it's a good bet you came to us
네, 당신이 우리에게 온 게 틀림없어요
It seems she has a man
그 사람한테 남자가 있는 것 같아
That must be it
그게 틀림없어
Otherwise, why would I suddenly kick you out?
그렇지 않으면 내가 왜 갑자기 널 쫓아내겠는가?
What do you mean by that?
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
Anyway, her husband is gone. What does it matter?
어쨌든 남편은 사라졌습니다. 그게 무슨 상관이야?
Do you want to be like the women of the Joseon Dynasty? Be a widow until death?
조선시대 여인처럼 되고 싶나요? 죽을 때까지 과부로 지내라?
I will go to Zhenyu's room to sleep
나는 Zhenyu의 방에 가서 자러 갈 것이다
You guys should go to sleep too
너희들도 자러 가야지
That room is very cold
그 방은 너무 추워요
She actually has a man
그녀에겐 사실 남자가 있어요
What's going on?
무슨 일이야?
Oh my god, I'm so shy...
맙소사, 너무 부끄러워요...
OMG…
세상에…
So shy
너무 부끄러워
These are the pajamas Tetsuo wore before I don't know if it looks good on you.
이건 테츠오가 예전에 입었던 잠옷이에요 당신에게 좋아 보이는지 모르겠습니다.
If you tell me beforehand I can buy your pajamas first
미리 말씀해 주시면 네 잠옷을 먼저 사줄게
Good night then
그럼 잘 자요
You know it will fit you even without wearing it.
입지 않아도 잘 맞을 거 아시죠?
After all, it's my son's pajamas
결국은 내 아들의 잠옷이군요
Brother Loyalty
형제 충성심
live with me
나랑 같이 살아
Three meals a day with you
하루 세 끼 너와 함께
Now I don’t want to miss it anymore
이제 더 이상 놓치고 싶지 않아
What you have suffered over the years
수년 동안 당신이 겪은 일
I will make it up to you
내가 해결해줄게
Brother Loyalty, I am satisfied now.
충성 형제님, 저는 이제 만족합니다.
Brother Zhongzhong, thank you
종중 형제님, 감사합니다
I will find a chance to tell Tetsuo
테츠오에게 말할 기회를 찾아볼게
Tell him about our relationship
그에게 우리 관계에 대해 말해줘
You see what I mean?
무슨 말인지 아시겠어요?
I know you said it many times
나는 당신이 그 말을 여러 번 말한 것을 압니다
if someone asks me
누군가 나에게 묻는다면
I would say the lady's son I delivered the baby myself
그 여자의 아들이라고 하겠다. 제가 직접 아기를 분만했어요
Don't worry
걱정하지 마세요
(Diagnosis Choi Young-sik) Is it non-obstructive azoospermia?
(진단 최영식) 비폐쇄성 무정자증인가요?
(Dean Luo Yaoquan) Dean, please
(학장 Luo Yaoquan) 딘, 제발
Because of the child’s father’s political leanings
아이 아버지의 정치적 성향 때문에
may affect His appointment as prosecutor
영향을 미칠 수 있다 그의 검사 임명
(Dean Luo Yaoquan)
(학장 Luo Yaoquan)
Dean, please help me
딘, 도와주세요
I only have that son left now
이제 그 아들만 남았어
If something goes wrong with him
그 사람에게 무슨 일이 생기면
I…
나는…
I won't survive, Dean.
난 살아남지 못할 거야, 딘.
please help me
제발 도와주세요
I will never forget this kindness
나는 이 친절을 결코 잊지 않을 것이다.
Keiko, you're back
케이코, 돌아왔어
Yes
예
How are you doing these days?
요즘 어떻게 지내세요?
Keiko, sorry
케이코, 미안해
can you go out for a moment
잠깐 나갈 수 있어?
OK
알았어
so
그래서
How do you answer
당신은 어떻게 대답합니까?
I was so scared that I couldn't speak
너무 무서워서 말을 할 수 없었어요
It was too late, but it was so fast that my husband happened to show up.
너무 늦었지만 너무 빨라서 남편이 우연히 나타났습니다.
Just say that Tetsuo is your biological son.
그냥 테츠오가 당신의 친아들이라고 말해주세요.
I've heard that if you want to serve in an important organization
중요한 조직에서 봉사하고 싶다면
A wealth survey will be conducted
자산 조사가 실시됩니다
But the other person always makes me feel a little unusual
그런데 상대방이 늘 나를 좀 이상하게 느끼게 만들어요
We are not in our hometown anymore He also came here
우리는 더 이상 고향에 없습니다 그 사람도 여기 왔었어
And…
그리고…
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
That person looks familiar
저 사람 낯익은 것 같아
When living in Lishui
리수이에 살 때
I have followed guests from Mrs. Chu's house before Passed by several times
나는 전에 추 부인 집에서 온 손님을 따라온 적이 있습니다 여러번 지나갔지만
That person looked very similar to the guest at that time
그 사람은 그 당시 손님과 매우 비슷해 보였습니다.
How is it possible
어떻게 가능합니까?
You must have read it wrong
잘못 읽으셨나봐요
I feel like that person seems to know something Just came to the door
그 사람 뭔가 아는 것 같아 방금 문앞에 왔어
It made me break out in a cold sweat
식은땀을 흘리게 만들었지
How is it possible
어떻게 가능합니까?
Is there something he should know?
그 사람이 알아야 할 게 있나요?
what
뭐
Please completely forget the wrong ideas in your mind
마음속의 잘못된 생각은 완전히 잊어주세요
Tetsuo is my son
테츠오는 내 아들이야
Got it?
알았어?
I also hope to forget
나도 잊어버리길 바래
But it's not something I can control
하지만 그건 내가 통제할 수 있는 게 아니지
you really are...
당신은 정말...
sorry
미안
I will talk to her well when I go back
돌아가면 잘 얘기할게요
Let's go first
먼저 가자
Get up quickly
빨리 일어나
please wait a moment
잠시만 기다려주세요
A studious mother
공부를 잘하는 어머니
Could you please help me with something?
뭔가 좀 도와주실 수 있나요?
what
무엇
Our family has caused a lot of trouble for you before.
우리 가족은 이전에 당신에게 많은 문제를 일으켰습니다.
If you come to help, you can also supplement the family income.
도움을 주러 오시면 가계 소득도 보충하실 수 있습니다.
I remember you were good at driving a cultivator, right?
경운기 운전을 잘했던 기억이 나죠?
Life is really full of surprises
인생은 정말 놀라움으로 가득 차 있어요
The person who always avoids me
늘 나를 피하는 사람
She actually asked me to do something for her
그녀는 실제로 나에게 자신을 위해 뭔가를 해달라고 요청했습니다.
I'm already this age He actually asked me to take a driver's license test
벌써 이 나이가 됐어 실제로 운전면허 시험을 보라고 하더군요
It's so ridiculous
너무 우스꽝스러워
Don't dwell on it, just help.
그것에 연연하지 말고 그냥 도와주세요.
No matter how I think about it, I feel She was afraid that I would reveal Tetsuo's life experience.
아무리 생각해도 느낌이 안 와 그녀는 내가 테츠오의 인생 경험을 공개할까 두려웠다.
She just wants me to stay by her side to monitor me
그 사람은 내가 자기 옆에 있기를 바랄 뿐이야 나를 감시하기 위해
Why can’t you let go of Tetsuo now?
왜 이제 테츠오를 놓지 못하는가?
How could I forget him
내가 어떻게 그 사람을 잊을 수 있겠어요?
If there was an eraser in the world that could erase memories Please bring it to me
세상에 기억을 지울 수 있는 지우개가 있다면 나에게 가져다주세요
You are really...
당신은 정말...
So you don't help me
그래서 당신은 나를 도와주지 않습니다
Of course I want to help
물론 나도 돕고 싶어
This way you can see it often My son who became a prosecutor
이렇게 자주 볼 수 있어요 검사가 된 아들
Try saying that again
다시 한번 말씀해 보세요
Then I will really...
그럼 난 정말...
I know... I just won't say it...
알아요... 말하지 않겠습니다...
Really
정말
What's so hard about driving?
운전이 뭐가 그렇게 어렵나요?
(Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong)
(최철웅 검사)
Come and see the urban renewal areas
도시재생지역을 보러 오세요
Now these three places are left
이제 이 세 곳이 남았네요
I think it would be best if everyone can buy it
다들 구매하시면 좋을 것 같아요
If you have to choose
꼭 선택해야 한다면
Just buy it here...
그냥 여기서 사세요...
(Boss of Star Industrial, Byun Hak-soo)
(스타산업 변학수 사장)
next time work
다음번에 일할 때
Just like this Jisoo you...
이대로 지수야...
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site Mobilization of gangsters leads to violent clashes)
(명당동 철거현장에서 폭력 충돌 발생) 조폭 동원으로 폭력 충돌 발생)
(Gangster mobilization leads to violent clashes Violent suppression of residents at Mingdangdong demolition site)
(깡패 동원은 폭력적인 충돌로 이어진다. 명당동 철거현장 주민 폭력 진압)
Choi Cheol-woong, congratulations on your appointment as prosecutor.
최철웅님, 검사로 부임하신 것을 축하드립니다.
I originally planned to keep my distance from you.
원래는 너랑 거리를 둘 생각이었어.
But you are now a prosecutor
하지만 당신은 이제 검사입니다
If I didn't come to say congratulations You will definitely be angry with me forever
내가 축하 인사하러 오지 않았다면 넌 분명 나한테 영원히 화를 낼 거야
That's why I made up my mind to come see you
그래서 널 만나러 오기로 마음 먹었어
That's right
좋아요
I was planning to do it if you didn't show up
너 안 오면 하려고 했는데
I'm going to sue you
나는 당신을 고소 할 것입니다
Shero
셰로
I heard a lawyer I know say
제가 아는 변호사가 이렇게 말하는 걸 들었습니다.
I was fined just for parking illegally on the red line. It would be difficult to become a prosecutor
레드라인에 불법 주차한 것만으로도 벌금을 물었습니다. 검사 되기 힘들겠다
So honestly I thought you had no chance
그래서 솔직히 난 너에겐 기회가 없다고 생각했어
You are truly amazing…
당신은 정말 대단해요…
If you miss it because of the fine It's a pity that I'm such a talented person.
벌금 때문에 놓치면 내가 이렇게 능력 있는 사람인 게 안타깝다.
The senior management of our unit is very discerning, right?
우리 부서의 고위 경영진은 매우 안목이 뛰어나죠?
Can boast enough
충분히 자랑할 수 있다
You are a disease
당신은 질병입니다
Do you and Brother Douxue meet often?
당신과 Douxue 형제는 자주 만나나요?
That silly boy
그 어리석은 소년
I moved again a while ago
얼마전에 또 이사했어요
i'm looking for him
나는 그를 찾고 있어요
He will come later
그 사람은 나중에 올 거예요
I called him
나는 그에게 전화했다
Really?
정말
You are very clever at times like this
당신은 이럴 때 정말 똑똑해요.
Does he know I'm here too?
그 사람도 내가 여기 있다는 걸 알고 있는 걸까?
I told him
나는 그에게 말했다
Will he do it because I'm here? If you want to hide from me, you won’t come.
내가 여기 있기 때문에 그 사람이 그 일을 할 것인가? 나에게서 숨고 싶다면 오지 않을 것입니다.
He will definitely come
그 사람은 꼭 올 거야
He is better than anyone They all still want me to become a prosecutor.
그는 누구보다 낫다 아직도 다들 내가 검사가 되기를 바라네요.
And I have something important to tell him.
Error 504 (Server Error)!!1504.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
What's going on
무슨 일이야
Promise me first that you won't be angry
화내지 않겠다고 먼저 약속해줘
OK I'm not angry
알았어 나 화난거 아니야
what's going on
무슨 일이야?
The prosecutor who came in at the same time as me Sitting in the box next to
나와 동시에 들어온 검사 옆에 있는 상자에 앉아
Because we received a report
신고를 받았기 때문에
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site)
(명당동 철거현장에서 폭력 충돌 발생)
Violent conflict in Mingdangdong Doggeng
명당동 도갱의 폭력 분쟁
The identities of the participants are still being investigated.
참가자들의 신원은 아직 조사 중이다.
But I was also shocked when I saw these photos
그런데 이 사진을 보고 저도 깜짝 놀랐어요
"Should I say something to him?"
"내가 그 사람한테 무슨 말이라도 해야 하나?"
"When I'm indecisive"
"내가 우유부단할 때"
(live acoustic guitar singing) "He left"
(라이브 어쿠스틱 기타 노래) "그는 떠났다"
"I gave my heart" Hello Prosecutor Choi, congratulations.
"나는 내 마음을 바쳤다" 안녕하세요 최검사님, 축하드립니다.
"I shed tears for him"
"나는 그 사람 때문에 눈물을 흘렸다"
How are you doing lately?
요즘 어떻게 지내세요?
"I will also dream..." You stinky gangster
"나도 꿈을 꿀 거야..." 냄새나는 깡패야
You moved behind my back Is this just for doing this?
당신은 내 등 뒤로 이동 단지 이 일을 하기 위한 것인가요?
Is that you in the photo?
사진에 있는 사람이 바로 당신인가요?
Yes
오른쪽
Where did these photos come from?
이 사진들은 어디서 나온 걸까요?
Sent by people
사람들이 보낸
This is what the underworld does
이것이 지하세계가 하는 일이다
If you want to teach me a lesson, just leave.
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Hello Cui Zhexiong
안녕하세요, 추이저시옹(Cui Zhexiong)
Why don't we just arrest him and imprison him?
그냥 체포해서 감옥에 가두는 게 어때요?
Why are you showing me these photos?
왜 나에게 이 사진들을 보여주나요?
You really haven't changed at all...
당신은 정말 하나도 변하지 않았네요...
Tetsuo, use your clever head Use it in the right place
테츠오, 영리한 머리를 써라 올바른 장소에 사용하세요
Dingchen…
딩첸…
Wait a minute...
잠시만요…
Every time the three of us meet It doesn't end well
우리 셋이 만날 때마다 좋게 끝나지 않아
Please don’t take photos like this again.
다시는 이런 사진을 찍지 마세요.
That's why I asked you to be a prosecutor
그래서 검사해 달라고 한 거야
what do you want me to do
내가 무엇을 하기를 바라나요?
If you get information like this Just help me, right?
이런 정보를 얻으면 그냥 도와주세요, 그렇죠?
Do you ask the prosecutor to protect gangsters?
검사에게 조폭을 보호해달라고 요구하는가?
have you forgotten
잊었니?
I know I still owe you
난 아직도 당신에게 빚진 걸 알아요
But it shouldn’t be repaid in this way, right?
하지만 이런 식으로 갚으면 안 되겠죠?
No matter if I'm a gangster or not
내가 갱스터든 아니든 상관없어
It doesn’t matter if you are a prosecutor or not.
당신이 검사인지 아닌지는 중요하지 않습니다.
You have to repay the debt you owe me Until I yell stop
나한테 진 빚은 갚아야지 내가 그만하라고 소리칠 때까지
I get it…
알겠어요…
But don’t involve Dingchen
하지만 Dingchen은 포함하지 마세요
Don't let her become unhappy because of you
너 때문에 그 사람이 불행해지도록 놔두지 마
I never involved her
난 그녀를 연루한 적 없어
That's why I moved
그게 내가 이사한 이유야
Also
게다가
Same for you
너랑 똑같아
I know you are afraid that Dingchen will be taken away by me
딩첸이 나한테 빼앗길까 봐 두려운 거 알아
why
왜
Because you are a sore loser
넌 지독한 패배자니까
But you figure it out
하지만 당신은 그것을 알아낼
This is not love, but possessiveness
이건 사랑이 아니라 소유욕이다
Brat
애새끼
Coming...
오는...
Brother, who is coming?
형님, 누가 오나요?
Don't know
모른다
Brother, please come in
형님 들어오세요
Thank you for your hard work, Boss Lian.
리안 사장님, 노고에 감사드립니다.
thank you
감사합니다
As long as you can do your part for the country
국가를 위해 자신의 역할을 할 수 있는 한
We are always ready to be dispatched
우리는 언제나 파견될 준비가 되어 있습니다
Hello…
안녕하세요…
Say hello
인사해
This is Team Leader Wu, our minister’s confidant.
우리 장관의 측근인 우 팀장입니다.
He is the person with real power in our unit
그 사람이 우리 부대에서 진짜 권력을 갖고 있는 사람이에요.
You know what I mean
내 말이 무슨 뜻인지 알잖아
Team leader Wu said he wants to see you So we came together
우팀장이 보고싶다고 하더군요 그래서 우리는 함께 모였습니다
My name is Lian Guangzhuo. Please give me some advice.
제 이름은 Lian Guangzhuo입니다. 조언 좀 부탁드립니다.
My surname is Wu
내 성은 우(Wu)입니다
This is the case The brother in charge of on-site command
이것이 사실이다 현장지휘를 맡은 동생
He and I are like sworn brothers in Taoyuan Guan Yu and Zhang Fei
그와 나는 타오위안의 의형제와도 같다 관우와 장페이
We are brothers
우리는 형제입니다
Come and say hello
와서 인사해
My name is Li Douxue
내 이름은 리두수(Li Douxue)입니다.
Have we met before?
우리 전에 만난 적 있나요?
Thank you for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
Although there was a bit of bloodshed
약간의 유혈사태가 있었지만
But you handled things well
하지만 넌 일을 잘 처리했지
thank you for your compliment
당신의 칭찬에 감사드립니다
Boss Lian, come here
리안 사장님, 이리 오세요
yes
응
It is said that apartment buildings will be built in more areas in the future.
앞으로는 더 많은 지역에 아파트가 들어설 것이라고 합니다.
Yes
예
I'll contract out the window frames for the apartment to you.
아파트 창틀을 당신에게 계약하겠습니다.
what
뭐
Won't you give me the right to move in?
나한테 이사할 권리를 주지 않을래?
Right of occupancy?
점유권?
Are you still not satisfied with this?
아직도 이것에 만족하지 못하시나요?
don't you know How much can you earn from window frames alone?
모르시나요? 창틀만으로 얼마를 벌 수 있나요?
That's not what I meant
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니었어
Section Chief Thank you
과장님 감사합니다
Why are you still dumbfounded? Let the lady come in quickly.
왜 아직도 멍청한 거야? 아줌마 빨리 들어오게 해주세요.
Section Chief
과장
I found one for you A special lady comes in
당신을 위해 하나 찾았어요 특별한 아줌마가 찾아온다
Really?
정말요?
I'm looking forward to it
나는 그것을 기대하고있다
Stay tuned
계속 지켜봐 주시기 바랍니다
Yeon Joo
연주
boss
보스
Just promise me once Wait a minute...
한번만 약속해줘 잠깐만요...
This is my first time asking you to do this
내가 너한테 이렇게 해달라고 부탁한 건 처음이야
I don't want
나는 원하지 않는다
Yeonjoo, I'm sorry
연주야, 미안해
I really don't want to go in
정말 들어가기 싫다
Yeon Joo, please save me just once.
연주씨, 한 번만 살려주세요.
ok
알았어
Boss, please let me go
사장님 저 좀 놔주세요
Don't you know very well that I hate this kind of thing the most?
내가 이런거 제일 싫어하는거 잘 알지?
Of course I know...
물론 알아요...
So just once is enough
그러니 한 번이면 충분해요
Yanzhu, please let me ask you for help
Yanzhu, 도움을 요청하겠습니다.
Today’s guest is a high-ranking guest
오늘의 손님은 고위 손님이십니다.
Go get acquainted It will also be very helpful to you
가서 친해지세요 당신에게도 많은 도움이 될 거예요
That's what you insist on I won’t be an actor anymore
그게 당신이 주장하는 것이에요 나는 더 이상 배우가 되지 않을 것이다
Hello…
안녕하세요…
Hey, I've been begging you so hard
야, 내가 그렇게 간절히 빌고 있었어
Do you really want to do this to me? Are you sure?
정말 나한테 이러고 싶은 거야? 확실합니까?
Boss, I just want to ask you not to do this to me.
보스, 나에게 이런 일을 하지 마시라고 부탁드리고 싶습니다.
You really want to drink wine as a penalty instead of eating the toast...
정말 토스트 대신에 벌칙으로 와인을 마시고 싶은데...
what is this doing
이게 뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Why don't you let go?
왜 놓아주지 않니?
Wait a minute, it hurts...
잠깐만요, 아파요...
You little bastard, let go now
이 새끼야 이제 놔
This woman is really...
이 여자는 정말...
my neck… Hello
내 목… 안녕하세요
Be more respectful
좀 더 존중해주세요
ok sorry
알았어 미안해
Hello…
안녕하세요…
I'm here to meet your boss
나는 당신의 상사를 만나러 왔습니다
Then please go in alone. She even said she didn't want to go in.
그럼 혼자 들어가세요. 심지어는 들어가고 싶지 않다고 하더군요.
what
무엇
Let's go
갑시다
Hello Song Yanzhu...
안녕하세요 송옌주님..
stop
멈추다
Wait a minute...
잠깐만요...
Why is it so noisy?
Why is it so noisy?
It hurts...
아프다...
Boss Yin, what are you doing before you come in?
인 사장님, 들어오기 전에 뭐하세요?
Where is Song Yeon-joo?
송연주는 어디있나요?
I want to ask you
나는 당신에게 묻고 싶습니다
This guy is the one who twisted my wrist
이 사람이 내 손목을 비틀었던 사람이야
Let Song Yanzhu run away
Let Song Yanzhu run away
Abominable
혐오스러운
what
뭐
Brother, sorry
Brother, sorry
Because Song Yanzhu doesn’t want to go in But he dragged her here
Song Yanzhu는 들어가기를 원하지 않기 때문에 But he dragged her here
Brat...
형님...
Don't you know how important this is?
이게 얼마나 중요한지 모르시나요?
Who are you? How dare you decide her stay or go without permission?
누구세요? 감히 그녀가 머물 것인지, 허락 없이 갈 것인지를 어떻게 결정합니까?
Brother, be gentle with your feet.
형제님, 발을 부드럽게 해주세요.
how are you
잘 지내세요?
Won't you get out of the way?
비켜주지 않을래?
Big brother
형님
Impolite brat
Impolite brat
Is this how you manage your younger brother?
동생을 이렇게 관리하는 건가요?
Catch Song Yanzhu quickly
빨리 송옌주를 잡아라
Go and get it back...
Go and get it back...
Big brother
형님
It's my fault. Hit me.
내 잘못이야. 나를 때리세요.
What are you guys like?
여러분은 어떤가요?
Hello Li Douxue
안녕하세요 리두수에
Now you teach him a lesson in front of me
이제 당신은 내 앞에서 그에게 교훈을 가르치고 있습니다
Brat, hurry up
형, 빨리요
Good job
잘했어
are you kidding
농담하는거야?
This is a lesson, you brat.
이건 교훈이다, 이 새끼야.
Get up...
일어나...
Hurry up and teach him a lesson
빨리 가서 그 사람에게 교훈을 가르쳐 주세요
You boy
당신은 소년
What do you want now?
지금 무엇을 원하세요?
Brat
녀석
enough
충분히
Yeon Joo
연주
Boss Yin, bring her in quickly
인보스 빨리 데려와
I'll settle the score with you later
나중에 너랑 점수 정할게
Do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
Boss Yin, hurry up
인 사장님, 서두르세요
Yanzhu, come here quickly...
옌주야 빨리 와라...
Hello, I am movie star Song Yeon-joo.
안녕하세요, 영화배우 송연주입니다.
I love watching your movies
나는 당신의 영화를 보는 것을 좋아합니다
I have read almost all of your works
나는 당신의 작품을 거의 다 읽었습니다.
Of course, while my wife is away
물론, 아내가 없는 동안
Sirs, please take a look
선생님들, 좀 보세요
She is both beautiful and good at acting
예쁘기도 하고 연기도 잘하고
It's just impeccable.
그것은 완벽합니다.
Thanks for the compliment
칭찬해주셔서 감사합니다
Let's listen to Miss Song Yeon-joo sing a song
송연주 선생님의 노래를 들어보세요
Come on, everyone applaud
자, 모두 박수를 쳐주세요
Thank you for your compliments
칭찬해주셔서 감사합니다
But I'm not going to sing
하지만 난 노래를 부르지 않을 거야
I’m not going to pour wine for you either.
나도 당신에게 포도주를 따르지 않을 것입니다.
Song Yanzhu, what’s wrong with you?
송옌주, 무슨 일이야?
I plan not to be Song Yeon-joo anymore
나는 더 이상 송연주가 되지 않을 생각이다
What you like Is it the movie star Song Yeon-joo?
당신이 좋아하는 것 영화배우 송연주인가?
My real name is Park Jung Mi
본명은 박정미 입니다
from this moment on
지금 이 순간부터
I'm not a movie actor, and I'm not Song Yeon-joo either.
저는 영화배우도 아니고, 송연주도 아닙니다.
I want to live as Park Jung Mi
박정미로 살고 싶다
Then I can go now
그럼 이제 가도 돼요
-what is she talking about -What's going on?
-그녀가 무슨 말을 하는 거야? - 무슨 일이에요?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Sorry, I took her away first.
미안, 내가 먼저 데리고 갔어.
Sorry, what should I do now?
죄송합니다. 이제 어떻게 해야 하나요?
Would you like a glass of soju with the omelette?
오믈렛에 소주 한 잔 하실래요?
Your tone of voice is too indifferent, right?
목소리 톤이 너무 무심한 것 같죠?
Don't look at me like this. I have a baby face.
나를 그렇게 보지 마십시오. 나는 아기 얼굴을 가지고 있습니다.
I don't drink with actors
나는 배우들과 술을 마시지 않는다
I just decided not to do it
그냥 안 하기로 했어요
I don't drink with my sister
나 언니랑 술 안 마셔
Egg hot compress is not effective for bruises
계란찜은 타박상에 효과적이지 않습니다
Apply this
이것을 적용하십시오
Apply ice once or twice and it won't hurt anymore
얼음찜질을 한두번 하면 더 이상 아프지 않아요
If the bruise spreads, apply warm compresses with a towel
멍이 퍼지면 수건으로 온찜질을 해주세요.
It will get better soon
곧 좋아질 거예요
Are you a gangster too? You know so much
너도 갱스터야? 당신은 너무 많은 것을 알고
I do know a lot
나는 많은 것을 알고 있다
The little bastard can at least fight back.
그 작은 놈은 적어도 반격할 수는 있다.
But in this circle you can only get beaten
하지만 이 서클에서는 맞을 수밖에 없지
If you go to the hospital, the news will spread
병원에 가면 소문이 퍼진다
Over time I became an expert on bruises
시간이 지나면서 나는 타박상 전문가가 되었다
If you're curious about other types of wounds Just ask me how to deal with it
다른 상처의 종류가 궁금하다면 어떻게 처리해야 하는지 물어보세요
What if you were hit with a stick and broke a bone?
막대기로 맞아 뼈가 부러졌다면?
What's wrong
무슨 일이야?
Don’t you know this?
당신은 이것을 모르십니까?
Of course you have to go to the hospital, idiot
당연히 병원에 가야지, 바보야
You are simply a psychopath
넌 그냥 사이코패스야
really sorry
정말 미안해
please forgive me
용서해주세요
It doesn’t matter…
Error 504 (Server Error)!!1504.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
I didn't come here to drink in the first place.
나는 원래 술을 마시러 여기에 온 것이 아니다.
I came here because I have something to discuss with Boss Lian.
리안 사장님과 상의할 일이 있어서 왔습니다.
So you don’t have to pay too much attention
그러니 너무 많은 관심을 기울이실 필요는 없습니다
Is there anything I can do to help?
제가 도와드릴 수 있는 일이 있나요?
I will definitely try my best to help
나는 확실히 최선을 다해 도움을 줄 것입니다
Only gives you the exclusive right to sell the window frame
창틀 판매에 대한 독점권만 부여합니다.
You must be dissatisfied
당신은 불만족스러워야합니다
How is it possible
어떻게 가능합니까?
Don’t just be responsible for driving away the demolition households
철거가구를 몰아내는 책임만 맡지 마세요
How about participating directly in the program?
프로그램에 직접 참여해 보는 것은 어떨까요?
What? Directly involved?
무엇? 직접적으로 관련되어 있나요?
Of course I want to
물론 나도 그러고 싶어
But we haven’t been able to raise that much money yet.
하지만 우리는 아직 그렇게 많은 돈을 모으지 못했습니다.
Boss Lian only needs to prepare 20% of the funds.
리안 사장은 자금의 20%만 준비하면 됩니다.
We can prepare the rest
나머지는 우리가 준비하면 돼
We will also personally allocate the land to be developed
개발할 토지도 직접 배정해드립니다
100% certain
100% 확실함
This is not just in Seoul
이건 서울에만 있는 게 아니다
It is a metropolitan plan that covers the entire metropolitan area.
수도권 전체를 포괄하는 광역계획입니다.
Of course the profits are astronomical
물론 수익은 천문학적이다.
But I have a condition
그런데 조건이 있어요
You say it
당신은 그것을 말한다
first
먼저
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
우리는 주식의 70%를 보유하고 있으며 귀하는 30%를 보유하고 있습니다.
We will give you 10% more shares
우리는 당신에게 10% 더 많은 주식을 줄 것입니다
because of money laundering and tax expenses
자금세탁과 세금비용 때문에
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
모두 Boss Lian의 주식에 포함되어 있습니다.
Got it
알았어요
Second, even in front of King Yama
둘째, 야마왕 앞에서도
I can't even tell you about our cooperative relationship.
우리의 협력 관계에 대해서도 말할 수 없습니다.
If this is violated
이를 위반한 경우
The consequences may be disastrous
The consequences may be disastrous
I swear
맹세해요
I will definitely be loyal to you
나는 반드시 당신에게 충성할 것입니다.
And…
그리고…
I have one more thing to ask you
한 가지 더 물어볼 게 있어요
Please tell me
알려주세요
Please walk slowly
천천히 걸어주세요
Please walk carefully and slowly
조심해서 천천히 걸어주세요
Douxue
두쉬
Did I go a little too far just now?
지금 내가 너무 멀리 갔나?
It's okay, brother
괜찮아, 오빠
But why does he come to you?
그런데 그 사람이 왜 당신에게 오나요?
nothing
아무것도
He just came to please me
그 사람은 그냥 나를 기쁘게 하려고 왔을 뿐이야
Continue to help him like you are doing now
지금처럼 계속해서 그를 도와주세요
Really
정말로
So boring
너무 지루해
That's right
그렇죠
I would have done it even if he didn't say it
그 사람이 말하지 않았어도 난 그렇게 했을 거예요
Hello Douxue
안녕하세요 Douxue
Don't be angry
화내지 마세요
After all I am the boss
결국 내가 사장이다
But he was embarrassed in front of the guests
하지만 손님들 앞에서는 당황스러워요
I'm too excited
너무 신난다
Right
오른쪽
This…
이…
You take it and treat your little brothers to delicious food.
당신은 그것을 가져다가 동생들에게 맛있는 음식을 대접합니다.
relax
긴장을 풀다
Thank you bro
고마워요 형
No. Let’s get off work.
아니, 퇴근하자.
Please walk slowly, brother
천천히 걸어가세요 형님
So crowded
너무 혼잡해서
where
어디서
here
여기
These funds alone are absolutely not enough
이 자금만으로는 절대 부족해요
No matter how hard I think, I can't think of a way
아무리 생각해봐도 방법이 떠오르지 않네요
drink
마시다
Cow, you can eat it from head to tail
소, 머리부터 꼬리까지 먹어도 돼
Not even willing to throw away the internal organs A nation that cooks and eats
내장까지 버릴 생각도 안 하고 요리해서 먹는 나라
It's probably just us
아마 우리뿐일 거야
We often come here to eat the offal soup
우리는 여기 곱창탕 먹으러 자주 온다
Yes
예
The eldest brother also said that we should be together for the rest of our lives. Brothers who show their sincerity to each other
큰 형님도 우리가 평생 함께해야 한다고 말씀하셨어요. 서로에게 진심을 전하는 형제들
Yes
예
That's why I came to see you again
그래서 다시 만나러 왔어요
Do you remember what I said?
내가 무슨 말을 했는지 기억하시나요?
The person who will inherit my country from now on
이제부터 내 나라를 물려받을 사람
This is not Li Douxue who became a monk halfway.
중간에 출가한 이두수가 아닙니다.
It’s you who worked hard with me when I was young
어렸을 때 나와 함께 고생해준 너야
you know tiger
너 호랑이 알지?
Will push his child off the cliff
그의 아이를 절벽에서 밀어낼 것이다
Then only raise children who can crawl back.
그러면 뒤로 기어갈 수 있는 아이만 키우세요.
you are like that
당신은 그렇군요
And that guy Douxue
그리고 그 남자 Douxue
It has nothing to do with eating offal soup with me.
It has nothing to do with eating offal soup with me.
Come
오세요
Thank you for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
우리는 주식의 70%를 보유하고 있으며 귀하는 30%를 보유하고 있습니다.
We will give you 10% more shares
우리는 당신에게 10% 더 많은 주식을 줄 것입니다
because of money laundering and tax expenses
자금세탁과 세금비용 때문에
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
모두 Boss Lian의 주식에 포함되어 있습니다.
I know
알아요
Second, even in front of King Yama
둘째, 야마왕 앞에서도
I can't even tell you about our cooperative relationship.
우리의 협력 관계에 대해서도 말할 수 없습니다.
If this is violated
이를 위반한 경우
The consequences may be disastrous
결과는 비참할 수 있습니다
Because we need to know what big brother is doing
왜냐면 형님이 무엇을 하는지 알아야 하니까요.
If there is a 30% stake in the development company
개발회사의 지분이 30%인 경우
How much money can you make
당신은 얼마나 많은 돈을 벌 수 있습니까?
Although only 30%
30%에 불과하지만
But development projects cost several billions Billions of dollars
그러나 개발 프로젝트에는 수십억 달러의 비용이 듭니다. 수십억 달러
Of course the income is at the level of a large company
물론 수입은 대기업 수준이지만
We…
우리는…
Eat this business
이 사업을 먹어라
This is a chance for brother
오빠한테는 기회야
They will get rid of big brother Leave the work to us?
그들은 큰 형을 제거할 것이다 우리에게 일을 맡기시겠습니까?
That's right
그렇죠
It doesn't matter to them who they do it for
누구를 위해 그 일을 하는지는 그들에게 중요하지 않습니다
What matters is how good that person is
중요한 건 그 사람이 얼마나 좋은지
Are you saying this is the level of a big company?
이게 대기업 수준이라는 겁니까?
Let's just vote
그냥 투표하자
Get out of this miserable situation
이 비참한 상황에서 벗어나세요
How long are we going to live like this?
우리는 언제까지 이렇게 살 것인가?
You should have guessed the other party’s identity, right?
상대방의 신원을 짐작했어야겠죠?
So what?
그래서 뭐?
You should consider carefully
신중하게 고려하셔야 합니다
Those people live in a different world than us
그 사람들은 우리와는 다른 세상에 살고 있어요
They can…
그들은…
Killing us without anyone noticing
아무도 모르게 우리를 죽여
Kill someone?
누군가를 죽여?
Kill us?
우리를 죽여?
Which organization is it?
어느 조직인가요?
Haven't you seen it before?
전에 본 적이 없나요?
South Korea's CIA
한국의 CIA
I'm so scared
너무 무서워요
You can quit if you're scared
무서우면 그만둬도 돼
Do you want to grab it?
그것을 잡고 싶습니까?
I heard you are selling drugs recently
최근에 약을 팔고 있다고 들었어
what
뭐
how do you know
어떻게 알아?
sorry
미안
Because money is tight recently So I sold it temporarily
최근 자금이 부족해서 그래서 임시로 팔았어요
I know you don't like it
당신이 그것을 좋아하지 않는다는 것을 알아요
I can stop doing it now...
이제 그만해도 되는데...
It doesn’t matter…
그것은 중요하지 않습니다…
When money is tight What does selling drugs have to do with it?
돈이 빡빡할 때 마약 판매가 그것과 무슨 관련이 있습니까?
But since we have to do it Why not make it bigger
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know. 왜 더 크게 만들지 않는가?
Brother help you
형이 도와줘
Now working in the underworld
지금은 지하세계에서 일하고 있어요
money is power
돈은 힘이다
If you want to make a name for yourself all over the country Even more so
전국에 이름을 알리고 싶다면 더욱 그렇죠
Selling drugs doesn't matter Just wait until you gain some weight and then stop selling it.
약을 파는 건 중요하지 않아 살이 좀 찔 때까지 기다렸다가 판매를 중단하세요.
Isn't it?
그렇지 않나요?
Brother, why did you suddenly say that?
형, 갑자기 왜 그런 말을 했어요?
Yongbi
용비
How long will you stay in the junior suite?
주니어 스위트룸에 얼마나 오래 머물 예정인가요?
Even if it's not a house with ninety-nine rooms
아흔 아홉 개의 방이 있는 집이 아니더라도
At least rent a decent house
최소한 괜찮은 집을 빌려
Let's fart comfortably in there
그 안에서 편하게 방귀를 뀌자
That way…
그렇게…
It’s interesting for me to choose a successor.
후임자를 선택하는 것은 나에게 흥미로운 일이다.
Big brother
형
But suddenly it expanded
근데 갑자기 확장되서
It would be dangerous if rumors spread
소문이 퍼지면 위험할 것 같아요
Even my eldest brother...
심지어 큰 형님도...
You give it a try
한번 시도해 보세요
Just treat it like a little tiger has to face it The last hurdle
그냥 작은 호랑이가 직면해야 하는 것처럼 대하세요 마지막 장애물
And I can't get involved in drugs. in related cases
그리고 나는 마약에 참여할 수 없습니다. 관련된 경우
You understand
당신은 이해합니다
I will keep it in mind, brother
명심하겠습니다 형님
No
아니요
why
왜
Why do you always say no?
왜 항상 거절하나요?
If you say no, can't we do it?
안 된다고 하면 우리는 할 수 없나요?
Well, I can't
글쎄, 난 못해
Am I your dog...
내가 당신의 개인가요?
Because I'm the boss
내가 사장이니까
Team Leader Wu, only we can know about this.
우 팀장님, 이 사실은 저희만이 알 수 있습니다.
Don’t let anyone else in the company know
회사 내 다른 사람에게 알리지 마세요.
Yes
예
But how much do you know
하지만 당신은 얼마나 알고 있나요?
I only know the minister and the chief of security
장관이랑 안보실장만 알아요
Don't fund them with company funds
회사 자금으로 자금을 조달하지 마십시오
Help them get a bank loan
은행 대출을 받도록 도와주세요
Can't leave them with us Transaction records
그들을 우리에게 맡길 수는 없어 거래기록
Got it
알았어요
Also
또한
In addition, we retain 10% of our equity
또한, 우리는 지분의 10%를 보유합니다.
I can't guarantee I'll still be sitting How long have you been in this position?
아직 앉아 있을 거라고는 장담할 수 없어 이 직책을 맡은 지 얼마나 되었나요?
It’s time for Team Leader Wu to prepare to retire.
이제 우팀장이 은퇴를 준비할 시간이다.
Isn't it?
그렇지 않나요?
thank you
감사합니다
Who told you to lie down
누가 누우라고 했어?
Lie down for me
나를 위해 누워
Douxue, wait a minute
듀스, 잠깐만요
Who allows you to call the boss by his name?
누가 상사의 이름을 부르도록 허용합니까?
Operation Captain
작전대장
Lie down
누워
Douxue, okay, stop fighting.
Douxue, 알겠습니다. 그만 싸우세요.
Hello
안녕하세요
If you dare to steal money again
감히 또 돈을 훔치려 한다면
I will definitely beat you to death next time
다음번엔 꼭 널 때려죽이겠어
Let's go, brother
가자, 형
are you okay
괜찮아?
Let me go, brat
날 놔줘, 얘야
Abominable
혐오스러운
1 million won
100만원
You just stole 1 million won Was he beaten like this?
방금 100만 원 훔쳤잖아 그 사람 이렇게 때렸어요?
And that money is not what I want to use
그리고 그 돈은 내가 사용하고 싶은 것이 아니다
I'm buying suits for the new boys.
나는 새로 온 남자아이들을 위한 양복을 사려고 해요.
Just took that money
그 돈만 가져갔어
In addition to paying rent and eating
집세를 내고 먹는 것 외에도
He doesn't let us spend money at all
그 사람은 우리가 돈을 전혀 쓰지 못하게 해요
Big brother learns from Li Dou
형은 Li Dou에게서 배운다
Really stingy
정말 인색하다
you
당신
Have you really never received any pocket money?
정말 용돈을 받아본 적이 없나요?
Yes, brother
응, 형
I live with the money from my family
나는 가족의 돈으로 산다.
Brother, I'm still borrowing money from my friends.
형님, 저는 아직도 친구들한테 돈을 빌리고 있어요.
Did they keep the money for themselves?
그들은 그 돈을 스스로 갖고 있었나요?
Otherwise, how could I...
그렇지 않으면 내가 어떻게...
How could I want to steal money?
내가 어떻게 돈을 훔치고 싶을 수 있겠습니까?
That guy spoke very nicely Say we are a family
그 사람이 말을 참 잘했네 우리는 가족이라고 해
Hey, can this be called a family?
아, 이걸 가족이라고 부를 수 있나요?
He doesn't think we are family
그 사람은 우리가 가족이 아닌 것 같아
Yongbi
용비
You take me in
당신은 나를 받아 들인다
I will help you take revenge
복수를 도와줄게
You and Dou Xue have been inseparable since we were in prison.
You and Dou Xue have been inseparable since we were in prison.
How do you want me to believe you?
내가 당신을 어떻게 믿기를 바라나요?
I learn from Dou
도우한테 배운다
I took all the money from the office safe
사무실 금고에 있던 돈을 다 가져갔어
30 million won
3천만원
I could have taken the money and run away
돈을 빼앗고 도망갈 수도 있었어
But I came to you
하지만 난 당신에게 왔어요
Because I want revenge
복수하고 싶으니까
I seem to be able to feel your sincerity
너의 진심이 느껴지는 것 같아
These are just the tip of the iceberg
이것들은 빙산의 일각에 불과하다
In Lian Guangzhuo's vault
Lian Guangzhuo의 금고에서
There is ten times more money than this
이것보다 10배 더 많은 돈이 있어요
I run errands for him every month So I know it very well
나는 매달 그 사람을 위해 심부름을 해준다. 그래서 나는 그것을 아주 잘 알고 있다.
Doesn’t Lian Guangzhuo dislike going to the bank?
Doesn’t Lian Guangzhuo dislike going to the bank?
indeed
과연
Now working in the underworld
지금은 지하세계에서 일하고 있어요
money is power
돈은 힘이다
Just steal Lian Guangzhuo's treasury
그냥 Lian Guangzhuo의 보물을 훔치세요
Each of my brothers can save a few million more
내 형제 각자는 수백만 달러를 더 절약할 수 있습니다.
Lian Guangzhuo and Li Douxue
Lian Guangzhuo와 Li Douxue
Let's get rid of them all in one go.
한 번에 모두 제거해 보겠습니다.
I want that too
나도 그걸 원해
But the timing doesn't seem right
그런데 타이밍이 좀 안 맞는 것 같다.
Hello
안녕하세요
What are you arguing about?
당신은 무엇에 대해 논쟁하고 있습니까?
what are you going to do
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
Don't move at all
전혀 움직이지 마세요
I am prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong
저는 최철웅 검사입니다
You are Yongpil
당신은 용필입니다
nice to meet you
만나서 반가워요
Actually
실제로
My target is not you, it’s Lian Guangzhuo
내 타겟은 너가 아니라 Lian Guangzhuo
You know Lian Guangzhuo
당신은 Lian Guangzhuo를 알고 있습니다
kick you out
당신을 쫓아내다
Take Li Douxue with you
Li Douxue를 데리고 가세요
Trying to find ways to strengthen his power everywhere
어디에서나 그의 힘을 강화할 방법을 찾으려고 노력 중입니다.
Selling alcohol in a bar and laundering money is the most basic thing
술집에서 술을 팔고 돈세탁을 하는 것은 가장 기본적인 일이다
He also helped the company suppress the labor union.
그는 또한 회사의 노동조합 탄압을 도왔다.
even use violence Force residents in Tugeng area to leave
심지어 폭력을 행사한다 투겡(Tugeng) 지역 주민 강제 이주
It's really a headache
정말 머리가 아프네요
But they don’t know what backing they have
하지만 그들은 자신들이 어떤 지원을 받고 있는지 모릅니다
It runs away as fast as a loach and is hard to catch
미꾸라지처럼 빨리 도망가서 잡기 힘들어요
now because of them
이제 그 사람들 때문에
The public opinion situation is very bad
여론 상황이 매우 안 좋다.
The government says it wants to protect citizens
정부는 국민을 보호하고 싶다고 밝혔습니다.
So…
그래서…
We have to catch someone to scare the monkeys
원숭이를 겁주려면 누군가를 잡아야 해요
to calm public opinion
여론을 진정시키려고
It has been decided from above
위에서부터 결정됐어
you can take over the organization
조직을 장악할 수 있다
Then learn from Lian Guangzhuo and Li Dou Give us the criminal evidence
그런 다음 Lian Guangzhuo와 Li Dou에게 배우세요. 범죄 증거를 제시해 주세요
Then we can quell the dissatisfaction of the people practice patriotism
그러면 국민의 불만을 잠재울 수 있다 애국심을 실천하다
You can also take revenge He can also take over the organization smoothly
복수도 할 수 있다 그는 또한 조직을 원활하게 인수할 수 있다
Kill two birds with one stone, kill two birds with one stone Isn’t it the best of both worlds?
일석이조, 일석이조로 두마리 새 죽이기 두 세계의 최고가 아닌가?
How is it
어때요?
Do you think I will believe you?
내가 당신을 믿을 것이라고 생각합니까?
Yongbi
용비
What are we doing catching a little fish like you?
너 같은 작은 물고기를 잡아서 우리는 무엇을 하고 있는 걸까?
Our goal is to catch big fish
우리의 목표는 큰 물고기를 잡는 것입니다
Even if your name is reported to the newspaper, no one will recognize it.
당신의 이름이 신문에 보도되더라도 아무도 알아보지 못할 것입니다.
At least like Lian Guangzhuo To be discernible
적어도 Lian Guangzhuo처럼 식별 가능
Don't look down on people
사람을 우습게 보지 마세요
No one knows what will happen in the future.
앞으로 무슨 일이 일어날지는 아무도 모릅니다.
Yes
예
So
그래서
Yongbi
용비
in this world
이 세상에서
Day and night coexist
낮과 밤이 공존한다
Can there be only flowers and plants in this world?
이 세상에 꽃과 식물만 존재할 수 있을까요?
Have rabbits that eat grass
풀을 먹는 토끼가 있어요
There must also be wild wolves and tigers that eat rabbits
토끼를 잡아먹는 야생늑대와 호랑이도 있겠지
The organization always needs someone to accept it
조직에는 항상 그것을 받아들일 누군가가 필요하다
Just accept it
그냥 받아들이세요
However
그러나
Don't get into big trouble and cooperate with us well
큰 문제 일으키지 마시고 잘 협조해주세요
OK
알았어
Hey, drive faster
야, 빨리 운전해
is…
는…
Did you know that during the Imjin Japanese Rebellion?
임진왜란 당시 알고 계셨나요?
General Yi Sun-shin refused to listen to Seonjo's words No troops were sent
이순신 장군은 선조의 말을 듣지 않았다. 병력은 보내지 않았다
Later I got slapped The story of joining the army in white clothes
나중에 뺨 맞았어 흰옷을 입고 군대에 입대하게 된 이야기
People who originally disobeyed the king’s orders It must be executed immediately
본래 왕의 명령을 거역한 사람들 즉각 실행해야 한다
But General Yi Sun-shin because of his great achievements
하지만 이순신 장군은 그의 위대한 업적 때문에
Seonjo gave him a gold medal to avoid death
선조는 그에게 죽음을 면하기 위해 금메달을 주었다.
No matter what you do wrong
뭘 잘못해도 상관없어
He can avoid death once
한번은 죽음을 피할 수 있다
A token like that
그런 토큰
This is the death-free gold medal
이건 무사 금메달
This document is really hard to get
이 문서는 구하기가 정말 어렵습니다
Don't go around showing off to others
남에게 자랑하려고 돌아다니지 마세요
OK, then I'll stamp it...
알았어, 그럼 스탬프 찍을게...
No, I'll finish pressing the fingerprint first
아니요, 먼저 지문 누르기를 완료하겠습니다.
If you press your fingerprint again, this document will be Save your life
다시 지문을 누르면 이 문서가 나옵니다. 당신의 생명을 구하십시오
Everything is done
모든 것이 완료되었습니다
(Certificate from the Supreme Prosecutor’s Office)
(대검찰청 확인서)
You are here
당신은 여기에 있습니다
Sorry I'm late
미안해요 늦어서요
It's okay. Please sit down.
괜찮아요. 앉으세요.
Do you want to order a drink first?
먼저 음료를 주문하시겠습니까?
It's okay, no need
괜찮아 필요없어
good
좋아
Thank you for thinking of me so much
저를 이렇게 생각해 주셔서 감사합니다.
But I'm retired
그런데 은퇴했어요
when
언제
yesterday
어제
So please find another actor
그럼 다른배우 찾아보세요
This movie will definitely be a hit
이 영화는 분명 흥행할 거야
This role is also suitable for you
이 역할도 당신에게 적합해요
And we will definitely give you dividends
그리고 우리는 확실히 당신에게 배당금을 줄 것입니다
If…
만약…
An actress who fell in love with a gangster
갱스터와 사랑에 빠진 여배우
Doesn't it matter?
상관없나요?
Not in a movie, but in real life
영화가 아닌 현실에서
I'm such a madman
난 정말 미친 사람이야
Do you remember the last time you came to the filming set? Pick up my gangster
마지막으로 촬영장에 오셨던 때를 기억하시나요? 내 갱스터를 잡아라
Yes
예
i like him very much
나는 그를 매우 좋아한다
I want to date him
나는 그 사람과 데이트하고 싶다
am i crazy
내가 미쳤어?
Thank you for coming to your appointment today
오늘 약속 장소에 와주셔서 감사합니다
Then I'll leave first
그럼 나 먼저 갈게
But you are really crazy
근데 너 진짜 미쳤어
Be careful not to choke. Eat slowly.
질식하지 않도록 주의하세요. 천천히 먹어라.
I have to finish eating quickly
빨리 식사를 끝내야 해
Go back to work on the case
사건을 다시 처리하러 가세요
Don't you have something important to tell me?
나한테 중요한 할 말 없어?
do you have a girlfriend
여자친구 있어요?
I heard other prosecutors
다른 검사들한테 들었는데
When I was in training school, I would be chased by girls.
양성소에 다닐 때에는 여자아이들에게 쫓기곤 했습니다.
Did you call me back out of curiosity?
궁금해서 다시 전화한 걸까요?
How
어떻게
Are you worried that your son won't get a wife?
아들이 아내를 얻지 못할까 봐 걱정되시나요?
not like that
그렇지 않아
that's why
그렇기 때문에
If you want to get married
결혼하고 싶다면
There will be one less officiant
주임이 한 명 줄어들 것이다
Forget it
잊어 버려
Let’s talk about it later
나중에 얘기하자
do you want coffee
커피 마실래?
Mom, you have a boyfriend
엄마, 남자친구 있어요
No
아니요
I was right, right?
내가 옳았어, 그렇지?
Actually…
사실…
That's great. That's great.
훌륭해요. 훌륭해요.
do you really think so
너 정말 그렇게 생각하니?
Of course
물론이다
My mother is so young and beautiful
우리 엄마는 너무 젊고 아름다워요
I have to stay alone in an empty house for the rest of my life Is this true?
평생 빈집에 혼자 있어야 해요 이것이 사실입니까?
I originally thought that if you didn't have a boyfriend
원래는 남자친구가 없으면 그럴 줄 알았는데
I want to introduce you to someone
당신에게 누군가를 소개하고 싶어요
so good
너무 좋아
Tetsuo
테츠오
Why, are you worried that I will object?
왜, 내가 반대할까 봐 걱정돼?
Is it because of dad?
아빠 때문인가요?
Didn’t dad have…
아빠는 없었는데...
Will my son help him pass on the incense of the Cui family?
내 아들이 추이 가문의 향을 물려줄 수 있도록 도와줄 수 있을까요?
However
그러나
what does that person do
그 사람은 무엇을 하는가
where did you meet How did we know each other?
어디서 만났어? 우리는 어떻게 서로를 알았나요?
he is a good man
그는 좋은 사람이야
I'll arrange to meet you later
나중에 만나기로 약속할게요
Really exciting
정말 신난다
My mother actually started falling in love
우리 엄마는 실제로 사랑에 빠지기 시작했어요
You are much better than me
당신은 나보다 훨씬 낫습니다
very cold
매우 추워요
You go in quickly
너 빨리 들어가라
You go back I'm leaving
너는 돌아가라 나는 떠난다
(Terrible outsider team)
(끔찍한 아웃사이더 팀)
The cheers from the audience came from the baseball stadium
관중들의 환호가 야구장에서 들려왔다
Hello Dingchen
안녕하세요 딩첸
If you convince Director Lee Chang-ho
이창호 감독을 설득한다면
You must let me sing a movie soundtrack
내가 영화 사운드트랙을 부를 수 있게 해주세요
If you don't let me sing
내가 노래하게 놔두지 않는다면
I'll pack my bags and go back to Lishui
짐을 싸서 리수이로 돌아갈게요
You'd better go back now
이제 돌아가는 게 좋을 거야
It's so late. Who is it?
너무 늦었어요. 누구입니까?
He came to congratulate me and said I could win the game today It’s already amazing
축하해주러 오더니 오늘은 내가 이길 수 있다고 하더군요 벌써부터 놀랍다
Tetsuo
테츠오
How is it
어때요?
Would you like grilled pork belly with soju?
삼겹살 구이에 소주 드실래요?
Hello Dingchen
안녕하세요 딩첸
why did you come
왜 왔어?
You're here to celebrate your mom's boyfriend.
당신은 엄마의 남자친구를 축하하기 위해 여기 왔습니다.
Then you should drink it with your mother Why come here to celebrate?
그럼 엄마랑 같이 마셔야지 축하하러 왜 여기에 오나요?
Are you unhappy that my mother has a boyfriend?
우리 엄마에게 남자친구가 있어서 기분이 안 좋나요?
No
아니요
It's not like you don't know her Can't you help her celebrate?
당신이 그 사람을 모르는 건 아니잖아요 그녀가 축하하도록 도와줄 수 없나요?
Yes, of course I can help her celebrate
네, 물론이죠. 축하할 수 있도록 도와드릴 수도 있어요
I just don't know Is this something I can help her celebrate?
I just don't know 이것이 그녀가 축하하도록 도와줄 수 있는 일인가요?
Sincere congratulations to your mother Tetsuo
테츠오 어머니께 진심으로 축하드립니다.
Tetsuo, you are so handsome
테츠오, 너 정말 잘생겼어
How many men in the world would congratulate their mother on her remarriage?
어머니의 재혼을 축하해줄 남자가 세상에 몇이나 될까요?
Tetsuo
테츠오
i wrote a song
내가 노래를 썼어
Do you want to listen to it?
듣고 싶나요?
good
좋아
"Things of the past"
"과거의 일들"
"Even if I try hard to remember, I will turn around."
"기억하려고 애써도 뒤돌아볼 것 같아요."
"There will still be sad eyes"
"아직 슬픈 눈이 있을 거에요"
What a fool
정말 바보 야
"Sader than separation"
"이별보다 더 슬프다"
"The words wish me happiness"
"말은 나에게 행복을 기원합니다"
"Like stars shining in the night sky"
"밤하늘에 빛나는 별처럼"
"On your pupils"
"당신의 학생에"
The more I listen to this song, the more it sounds like it
이 노래는 들을수록 너무 좋은 것 같아요
Singing about my state of mind
내 마음 상태를 노래해
Really?
정말요?
"Tears flow emptyly"
"하염없이 눈물이 흐른다"
Those stinky dogs
냄새나는 개들아
What happened to them
그들에게 무슨 일이 일어났는가
Brother, leave it to me to solve it
형님, 해결은 나한테 맡겨주세요
As for fighting studies
격투 연구에 관해서는
It's your responsibility to stop him
그를 막는 것은 당신의 책임입니다
Never fail
절대 실패하지 마세요
If Douxue comes to help big brother Things are going to get tricky
Douxue가 형을 도우러 온다면 일이 꼬이게 될 거야
What's wrong
무슨 일이야?
who are you
당신은 누구입니까?
Wait
잠깐
Big brother…
형…
What's wrong? What's wrong?
무슨 일이야? 무슨 일이야?
Brother, please take the secret passage and escape.
형님, 비밀통로를 타고 탈출해주세요.
these bastards
이 새끼들
where has he gone
그 사람 어디 갔어?
Who?
누구?
You are here
당신은 여기에 있습니다
who are you
당신은 누구입니까?
It's Yongpil
용필이에요
You came just in time
딱 맞춰 오셨네요
Sure enough, you are the only one I can rely on
당연하지, 내가 의지할 사람은 너뿐이야
They were sent by Douxue, right?
Douxue가 보낸 것 맞죠?
I knew he would be like this
난 그 사람이 이럴 줄 알았어
But Yongpil
그런데 용필
how do you know i'm here
내가 여기 있는 걸 어떻게 알아?
That's right. How would I know?
맞습니다. 내가 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
Yongbi
용비
Although the sneak attack was successful
기습공격은 성공했지만
But he kept resisting
하지만 그는 계속 저항했다
It's a bit laborious
좀 힘드네요
Thank you for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
Big Brother, your favorite Douxue is here
빅 브라더, 당신이 가장 좋아하는 Douxue가 여기 있습니다
"Can I come back to you again?"
"다시 연락해도 될까요?"
"trembling eyes"
"떨리는 눈"
"Looks more sad"
"더 슬퍼 보여요"
"My heart is swaying in the desolate sky"
"황량한 하늘에 내 마음이 흔들리고 있어요"
"Your name is deeply etched in my heart"
"당신의 이름은 내 마음속에 깊이 새겨져 있습니다"
(Preview of next episode)
(다음화 예고)
Prosecutor Choi might have a chance Can you handcuff me?
최 검사에게 기회가 있을 수도 있다 나에게 수갑을 채워줄 수 있나요?
I said
나는 말했다
what was said
무슨 말을 했는지
break up
헤어지다
(Wu Wanxu) This is an item confiscated from Lian Guangzhuo's house.
(우 완수) Lian Guangzhuo의 집에서 압수한 물건입니다.
I found the mastermind
주인님을 찾았어요
who is
누구야?
before becoming a family
가족이 되기 전에
There's something I need to let you know first
먼저 알려드릴 게 있어요
Dingchen
딩첸
If I don’t join the underworld anymore
내가 더 이상 지하 세계에 합류하지 않는다면
Do you want to live with me?
나와 함께 살고 싶나요?
you
당신
None of them are human
그들 중 누구도 인간이 아니다
Go to hell
지옥으로 가세요
This is the hound you killed me price that must be paid
이게 네가 날 죽인 사냥개야 지불해야 할 가격